Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs, posters, 1998; RG0055 Series 43; 1 Linear feet (Box 1, Flat box 1)
  This series includes programs and posters from 1998.
  Formerly ACC# 699
  - Pan American Symphony, 02/28/1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    1 poster, 1 flier, 2 programs
  - North American Elite Youth Orchestra, 02/18/1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ballet Hispanico, 02/13/1998-02/14/1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1 poster, 2 programs
  - WAMMIES, 01/27/1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Homecoming Step Show, 01/31/1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    1 poster
  - Seoul Chamber Orchestra, 02/17/1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kissing a Fool, 02/24/1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Southern Exposure, 02/23/1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    2 postcards
  - Holi '98, 02/27/1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Global Divas, 03/26/1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    1 flyer, 2 programs
  - Sounds of Tempyo, 03/25/1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Law Revue, 03/07/1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Harmony Sweepstakes, 03/14/1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 45th Annual Washington International Competition for Singers, 03/15/1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Pirates of Penzance, 03/21/1998-03/22/1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - International Night, 03/29/1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bale Folclorico da Bahia, 03/31/1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Med School Follies, 04/04/1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Parisa, 05/02/1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chaplin Films, 04/18/1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - University Orchestra, 04/19/1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CFC Victory Celebration, 04/20/1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    2 programs, 1 poster
  - Right to Organize, 04/24/1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - University Wind Ensemble & University Symphony Band Spring Concert "Tribute to Dance", 04/26/1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - University Singers Concert, 04/25/1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - WCO, 05/01/1998-05/03/1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Parisa, 05/02/1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Kronos Quartet, 05/08/1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/15/1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GSEHD, 05/16/1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Medical School, 05/17/1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Washington Ballet, 05/21/1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - World Magic Summit, 05/23/1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Russian Festival Concert, 05/30/1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - EHD w/ Vinx, 05/31/1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Viva el Tango, 06/05/1998-06/06/1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Georgetown Day School, 06/07/1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Turquie: La Belle from Turkey, 06/19/1998 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ardha Nareeswaram, 06/20/1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Revolution '98, 06/14/1998 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Danzas Venzuelas, 07/05/1998 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Programs, flyers, posters, 1998-1999; RG0055 Series 44; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes programs, flyers, and posters from the fall 1998 to spring 1999.
  Formerly ACC#738
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    NMAH-Smithsonian Jass Masterworks Orchestra, Opera International The Barber of Seville, KanKouran West African Dance Company's 15th Anniversary Concert Jubilee, (2 copies of each)
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    The National Arabic Music Ensemble of the Cairo Opera House Egypt, GWU Medical Center Convocation and White Coat Ceremony, 13th Annual Wammies, (2 copies of each)
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Washington Concert Opera, The Whirling Dervishes of Turkey and the Mevlevi Ensemble in a Performance of Spiritual Music and Dance, The National Heritage Fellowships, Anthony Shay's AVAZ International Dance Theater Celebration of Silk Road, (2 copies of each)
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Harvest of Harmony "Put on a Happy Face," President's Night Judy Collins, The International Conservatory of Music's The John E. Marlow Guitar Series, (2 copies of each)
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    University Wind Ensemble & University Symphonic Band Fall Concert "Band President's Night," Washington Performing Arts Society, Teev Productions Chava Alberstein & The Klezmatics, (2 copies of each)
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    GWU Department of Music University Symphony Orchestra Fall Concert, Pan American Symphony Orchestra, Grammy in the Schools Career Handbook
  - Programs, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    The Korean Central Presbyterian Church (2 copies), The Washington Revels The Christmas Revels (2 copies), Music Concert with Young Ok Shin, Christine Kwak, and Sung Bin Kim
  - Programs, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Pan American Symphony Orchestra, Live at Lisner Auditorium Flamenco with Carmen Linares, (2 copies of each)
  - Guitarist John Williams, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sacred Dance of Tibet, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Whirling Dervishes with Kani Karaca and the Mevlevi Ensemble, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Egyptian American Cultural Association and Egyptian Cultural Bureau present The National Orchestra for Arabic Music, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - City at Peace presents Lockdown, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marisa Monte, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Navidad a lo Venezolano "El Conde Del Guacharo", undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Music Concert with Young Ok Shin, Christine Kwak, and Sung Bin Kim, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    3 large posters
  - KanKouran Presents Jubilee, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Programs, flyers, posters, 1998-1999; RG0055 Series 45; 1 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs, flyers, posters and booklets from 1998-1999.
  Formerly ACC#756
  - Buto-Sha Tenki, 02/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Paul Taylor II, 02/10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Raas Rage, 02/13/1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Northern Virginia Youth Symphony with Arturo Sandoval, 02/14/1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Pan American Symphony presents Luisa Fernanda, 02/20/1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    2 programs & 1 poster
  - Holi Rangeela, 02/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harmony Sweepstaker a Cappella Festival, 02/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1 program
  - Law Revue XXI, 03/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    3 programs
  - Margaret Cho, 03/09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - David Sedaris, 03/10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    1 signed poster
  - Cirque Eloize, 03/12/1999-3/14/1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dance and Music of Bali, 03/17/1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 03/19/1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Quartetto Gelato, 03/20/1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington DC, 03/27/1999-03/28/1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Think About Law Career Forum, 04/19/1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Med School Follies, 04/10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - International Night, 04/11/1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Spring Pops Concert, 04/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - University Singers, 04/17/1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - University Symphony, 04/18/1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Secret Garden, 04/22/1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Conjunto Norteno, 04/24/1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Opera International The 3 Bass-Baritones, 04/25/1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - WCO Linda Di Chamounix, 04/30/1999-05/02/1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Spain's Musical Exile and Its Legacy in the Americas, 05/01/1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1999 Sousa National High School Honour Band, 05/08/1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - An evening with Renouwned Everest Climber David Breashears, 05/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - A tribute to ArchBishop Tutu, 05/14/1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Graduate School of Education & Human Development, 05/15/1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - School of Public Health and Health Services, 05/15/1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/15/1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Doctor of Medicine Program, 05/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Annual Spring Performance Washington School of Ballet, 05/27/1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - David Murray Big Band, 06/05/1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    1 booklet
  - GDS Graduation, 06/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - High On You, 06/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bijan and Ebi, 06/19/1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Seoul Metropolitan Dance, 06/25/1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Commemoration of the 50th Anniversary of the Korean War, 06/25/1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Convocation in honor of Mubarak, 06/29/1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Programs, posters, 1999; RG0055 Series 46; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes programs and posters from 1999.
  Formerly ACC#790
  - Yellow River Art Ensemble, 12/18/1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Yellow River Art Ensemble and GW Chinese Students and Scholars Association. 2 programs
  - Christmas Revels, 12/02/1999-12/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: Washington Revels. 2 programs. Performances on Dec 2, 3, 4, 5, 10, 11, and 12
  - Cheb Mami, 11/23/1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: Teev Productions
  - Italia in Musica, 11/21/1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: Italian Cultural Society of DC. 2 programs
  - Sankai Juku, 11/19/1999-11/20/1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: WPAS. 2 programs
  - Millenium Convocation, 11/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsor: GW Special Events. 2 programs
  - George Winston, 11/15/1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: Chesapeake Concerts. 2 programs
  - Simon Shaheen, 11/13/1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sponsor: EACA. 2 programs
  - City at Peace: Beyond Me, 11/10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Sponsor: City at Peace. 2 programs
  - Fahir Atakoglu, 11/07/1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Sponsor: GWU and the Turkish Embassy. 2 programs
  - Harvest of Harmony, 11/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Sponsor: DC Barbershop Harmony Society. 2 programs
  - Earth, 11/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sponsor: Global Performing Arts. 2 programs
  - University Band, 11/02/1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Sponsor: GW Music Department
  - Darpana: Dance Reflections, 10/29/1999-10/31/1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Sponsor: IDEA. 3 programs
  - Real World, 10/27/1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Sponsor: GW Program Board. 2 Flyers
  - Enrico Macias, 10/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Sponsor: Teev Productions. 2 programs, 3 postcards
  - Azerbaijan, 10/23/1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Sponsor: US Azerbaijan Chamber of Commerce. 2 programs
  - Cesaria Evora, 10/22/1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Sponsor: Lisner Auditorium. 1 promotional CD
  - Arlo Guthrie, 10/21/1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - University Symphony, 10/17/1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Sponsor: GW Music Department. 2 programs
  - The Last Angry Brown Hat, 10/03/1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Sponsor: Smithsonian Associates. 2 programs
  - Patti Page, 10/04/1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Sponsor: Supreme Council. 2 programs
  - Pour Antigone, 10/02/1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Sponsor: Mathilde Monnier Dance Company and Lisner Auditorium. 2 programs
  - National Heritage Fellowships, 09/30/1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Sponsor: National Endowment for the Arts. 2 programs
  - PASO, 09/25/1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Sponsor: PASO. 2 programs, 2 season brochures, 3 postcards
  - Medical Center Convocation and White Coat Ceremony, 09/24/1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Sponsor: GW Medical Center. 2 programs
  - Tribute to Hank Williams, 09/24/1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Sponsor: Smithsonian Associates. 2 flyers
  - Monastic Dance of Tibet, 09/11/1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Sponsor: Program Board and International Campaign for Tibet. 2 programs, 2 postcards
  - Spirit of Indonesia, 09/09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Sponsor: Indonesian Community Association. 2 programs
  - KanKouran, 09/09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Sponsor: KanKouran. 2 programs, 2 flyers
  - Tosca, 08/06/1999-08/08/1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Sponsor: Opera International. 2 programs. Performances on Aug. 6 and 8
  - Cheb Mami, 11/23/1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Teev productions. 3 posters
  - George Winston, 11/15/1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: Chesapeake Concerts
  - Iva Bittova, 11/14/1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: Embassy of the Czech Republic
  - Earth, 11/04/1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: Global Performing Arts
  - Darpana: Dance Reflections, 10/29/1999-10/31/1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: IDEA
  - Enrico Macias, 10/26/1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gilberto Gil, 09/15/1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: WPAS and Lisner Auditorium
  - Monastic Dance of Tibet, 09/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Sponsor: Program Board and International Campaign for Tibet
  - Spirit of Indonesia, 09/09/1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Sponsor: Indonesian Comm. Association
  - KanKouran, 09/04/1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Sponsor: KanKouran
  - David Murray Big Band, 05/05/1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Sponsor: Smithsonian Associates
  - Secret Garden, 04/29/1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Sponsor: Exceptional Artists
- Programs, posters, 1999-2000; RG0055 Series 47; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs and posters for the 1999-2000 season.
  Formerly ACC#848
  - The Christmas Revels, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fahir Atakoglu, 11/07/1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Swing Time, 02/04/2000-02/05/2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1 program & 1 flyer
  - David Broza, 02/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    2 programs, 1 poster, 1 postcard
  - Music for the Millenium, 02/10/2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Seafaring Son Rhythms of Mexico, Andalucia, Africa and the Carribean, 02/12/2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Troubs Festival 2000, 02/18/2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Step Show, 02/19/2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Blues Hall of Fame, 02/22/2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University Symphony Spring Concert, 02/25/2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Holi Rangeela 2000, 02/26/2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Service for Amatu'l Baha Ruhiyyih Khanum, 02/27/2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Law Revue, 03/04/2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Johansen Competition, 03/12/2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington Lights Camera Action, 03/18/2000-03/19/2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Harmony Sweepstakes, 03/25/2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2000 String Competition, 03/26/2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Danny, Gidi, Mazi, 03/28/2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Med School Follies, 04/01/2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Duo Pianists, 04/03/2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - An Evening at the Capitol City, 04/07/2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Sima Bina, 04/08/2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mary Black, 04/09/2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Student Honors Recital, 04/10/2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Rodrigues, 04/12/2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - International Night, 04/14/2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Into the Woods, 04/27/2000-04/30/2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Goyescas, 05/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    1 poster, 1 postcard
  - Arka Ballet, 05/07/2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    2 poster, 2 postcard, 2 programs
  - Yehoram Gaon, 05/11/2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Gateway Music Festival, 05/13/2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Audra McDonald, 05/14/2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/19/2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Graduate School of Education and Human Development, 05/20/2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Doctor of Medicine Degree Program, 05/21/2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Jewish Song and Renaissance, 05/23/2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Annual Spring Performance Washington School of Ballet, 05/25/2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Eric Charles McGee and Friends, 06/02/2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - An Evening of Chinese Music and Dance, 06/03/2000 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    1 poster and 2 programs
  - The School Without Walls Graduation, 06/09/2000 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Dance Institute of Washington, 06/10/2000 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Georgetown Day School Graduation, 06/11/2000 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Celebrating Our Voice, 06/17/2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Dance Journey Exploring Dance in Washington, DC, 06/28/2000 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Milton Nascimento, 06/23/2000 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    1 photo - signed, 1 poster - signed
- Programs, ledgers, 1940-1999; RG0055 Series 48; 21 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 14, Box 1, Box 6, Box 7, Box 4, Box 5, Box 10, Box 11, Box 8, Box 9, Box 12, Box 13)
  This series includes programs for performances/events at Lisner auditorium, 1940-1999. One box has ledgers and date books from 1950's-1980's.
  Formerly ACC# 934
  - Photocopied newspaper clippings, 1940-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1940-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Address books, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Two year personal plan book, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ledger book, 10/1950-06/1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Planning calendar, 09/1965-08/1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Planning calendar, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1946-1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Columbia Light Opera Company in Sigmund Romberg's "The New Moon," November 20-23, 1946; Iva Kitchell, 1957; Inbal Dance Theater of Israel, 1958
  - Programs, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Japanese Music and Dance, October 1; The Opera Society of Washington "Vanessa," "Tosca," eighth season; "In Memorium John Fitzgerald Kennedy", November 27
  - Programs, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    The Opera Society of Washington "Maria Golovin"
  - Programs, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    The Friday Morning Music Club presents "Jose Greco and his Gypsies" January 27-28
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    The Opera Society of Washington "Bomarzo," (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Washington Performing Arts Society "Sabicas: Flamenco Guitarist", "Victor Borge" "Hilharmonica Hungarica Oskar Werner" and "Carlos Montoya;" Friends of the Alley Library "A Musical Salute to Walter E. Washington and Thomas W. Fletcher, October 22 (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society pamphlet
  - Programs, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Opera Society of Washington presents Gian Carlo Menotti's Amahl and the Night Visitors (Opera in one act) and The Medium (Tragedy in two acts), Dec. 7, 9-10; Washington Performing Arts Society pamphlet; The Johann Sebastian Bach International Competitions, May 24-26; El Teatro Colon de Buenos Aires; Washington Performing Arts Society
  - Programs, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    The Opera Society Of Washington subscription form; "Nana Mouskouri, December 14; Washington Performing Arts Society; U.S. Navy Band "Salute to Patriotism;" "Two Faces of India" a program of classical dances and yoga, Sept. 20; "The Believers" the black experience in song, Oct. 27; "David Bean," Pianist, Nov. 9 (2 copies); Washington National Symphony; "The Nutcracker (2 copies);" "Music from Marlboro; "The Turn of the Screw," Nov. 28, 30, Dec. 3; Friday Morning Music Club "Instrumental Ensemble," Dec. 11 (2 copies); Johann Sebastian Bach International Competitions, Sept. 26-28; The National Ballet "America's Classical Ballet," Nov. 7 (2 copies, 1 signed); "Washington Symphony Musicians In Concert," Nov. 13 (2 copies); "Concert by the Camerata Bariloche, Nov. 10 (2 copies); "Le Comete Ory," Oct. 17, 19, 22 (2 copies); "The Al Huang Dance Concert," June 26-27 (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Washington Performing Arts Society, book 4 & 5; "Koanga" by Frederick Delius (2 copies); "Abbey Simon" (2 copies); Friends of the National Ballet membership form (2 copies); "Swan Lake;" "America's Classical Ballet, (2 copies); "Cinderella" (2 copies); "America's Classical Ballet: Cinderella" (2 copies both signed); "D.C. Music Scene + 1" (2 copies); Igor Kipnis Harpsichordist (2 copies); "Ceremony for the Presentation of the Commemorative Insignias" (2 copies); "The Henry Miller Odyssey" (2 copies); "Coppelia" (2 copies); "Swan Lake La Sylphide" (2 copies); "Evelyn Crochet" (2 copies); Class of 1970 Commencement at Frank W. Ballou High School; "Banco Interamericano de Desarrollo"; Rafael Puyana, Harpsichordist; International Night; "The Trinidad Steelband"; "An Evening with Edward Villella"; "Theatre on the Ballustrade of Prague"; The MIT Symphony Orchestra (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    "Chopin Memorial Concert" (2 copies); The V Inter-American Music Festival (2 copies); "25th Anniversary Concert Montgomery County Youth Orchestra" (2 copies); The International Series "Ballet Spectacular" (2 copies); V Inter-American Music Festival "Chamber Opera of the Colon Theatre" (2 copies); Miss Teenage Metropolitan Washington Pageant (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    The United States Marine Band "The President's Own" Salute to Patriotism; Ballet Spectacular 10th Anniversary season; "The Owl and the Pussycat;" The National Ballet "The Nutcracker" (2 copies); 25th Congress of the International Fiscal Association List of Congress Members and Guests; Commencement of the Washington Hospital Center "School of Nursing;" The XXV Congress of The International Fiscal Association "Leontyne Price" with the National Symphony Orchestra (2 copies, 1 signed)
  - Programs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    National Symphony Orchestra "Rusalka" (2 copies); The Atlanta Skin Diving Council & The National Association of Underwater Instructors "Inward to the Sea an Undersea Symposium" (2 copies); The Washington Civic Opera Association w/National Symphony Orchestra "Don Pasquale" (2 copies); The Capitol Ballet Guild, Inc. "Capitol Ballet Company in Concert" (2 copies); Republic of Guinea "Djoliba National Ballet" (2 copies); Embassy of Chile "Ballet Folklorico de Chile Pucara" (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society in "Le Barbier de Seville" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Regional Ballet Company "Coppelia" (2 copies); BOAC & PanAm "Non-Stop Britain '72" (2 copies); The United Holy Land Fund "The Egyptian Comedy Troupe" (2 copies); Ballet-Theatre Contemporain "BAM" (2 copies); GWU Speech and Drama Dept. "A Mid-Summer Night's Dream;" Series of Talks by Sun Myung Moon "The Day of Hope" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Armenian Students Association "Charles Aznavour" (2 copies); Banco InterAmericano de Desarrollo Asociacion de Empleados "Acto de entrega de insignias de cinco y diez anos de sericio" (2 copies); GWU "Dedication of the GWU Library" (2 copies); Regional Ballet Company of Washington 1973 Season (2 copies); Wolf Trap American University Program for the Performing Arts "The Modern Dance Series" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    An Evening of Christmas Music from Spain and the Americas with the Inter-American Chamber Singes (2 copies); Ballet Spectacular Gala (2 copies); Commencement Exercises "Immaculate Conception Academy of St. Stephen Martyr Parish;" Korean Musical Drama "Love Story of Yi Dynasty;" The Washington Civic Opera Association "The Gypsy Baron"
  - Programs, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Mercedes Sosa Canta A Latino-America (2 copies); Students of Soodo Women's Teacher's College "God is Love (Korean Ballad) A Legendary Story of the Woodcuter and the Heavenly Princess" (2 copies); Argentina in Concert (2 copies); Washington Civic Opera Association w/ National Symphony Orchestra "Die Fledermaus" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    The Embassy of Korea "Korea Night" (2 copies); Inward to the Sea (2 copies); The Awaji Puppet Theatre (2 copies); Inter-American Music Festival (2 copies); The Catholic University of America-School of Music "Opera '74" (2 copies); Free and Accepted Masons "The Mecca Melodiers of Mecca Tmepla No. 10" (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society "Rudy Perez Dance Theatre" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Commencement Exercises for Immaculate Conception Academy of St. Stephen Martyr Parish (2 copies); Itzhak Perlman In Concert (2 copies); The Czechoslovak Society of Arts and Sciences "Bedrich Smetana's Two Widows" (2 copies); Festival of the Nations (2 copies); Children's Morning Concert (2 copies); Commencement of the Washington Hospital Center School of Nursing (2 copies); International Brotherhood of Police Officers Local No. 442 "Roy Radin Vaudeville Revue" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)